美国华纳兄弟影片公司
听我说  这里正在发生
Take it  I'll tell you what  we're having an earth
美国威秀影片公司联合出品
片名:《明日边缘》
可以开始了
start talking.
不知道能不能播出去
I'm not sure if we're even on the air.
应该说
Uh  this is uh
这是一系列爆炸
a series of explosions
这是一起严重的事件
This is a major incident
这场严重的突发事件
The emergency is a major incident
撞击产生爆炸的瞬间
That's a meteor hit.
一场严重的入侵事件
It does now appear to be a major attack
自从五年前降落在汉堡市境外
Since they landed outside Hamburg five years ago
它们已经横扫了整个欧洲大陆
they have steadily advanced across Europe.
我们已经损失了几百万人
We've suffered millions of casualties and yet
各国政府要员目前已经开始撤离了
The evacuation of key government officials continuing
很显然我们无力阻止它们
Nothing we have done has been able to stop their advance
在人员方面 欧洲
Human costs   the Europeans
已经付出了高昂的代价 它们有模仿能力
- have paid the highest  - They appear to mimic
甚至超越我们的的各种行为
and even anticipate our actions
如果不能在法国打败它们
We could not defeat them in France
就得在伦敦街头跟他们较量
we'll be fighting them in the streets of London
然后是纽约  东京
then New York   then Tokyo.
这是一场生死之战
All of humanity is at stake.
五年后  我们终于取得了胜利
After five years   we finally have a victory.
这是从凡尔登传回的画面
These pictures are just in from Verdun.
值得称道的是这次胜利伤亡少、损害低
And the coalition victory was how low casualties were
应该说这的确是一场了不起的胜利
We have seen a stunning victory here today.
联合防御军
The United Defense Force
你怎么才能让人们相信
How do you convince people
这场战争我们必胜
that this is a fight that can be won?
这是外星人对全球的侵略战争
This is an alien invasion and a global war.
有了新型战甲技术和很少的训练
With the new jack in technology and limited amount of training
我们就能创造出超级战士
we've been able to create super soldiers.
瑞塔・沃塔斯基 就是凡尔登的天使
Look at Rita Vrataski   The Angel of Verdun
无论从速度还是力量上来看
They're calling her
她都可以说是
The Angel of Verdun
她被看成是这场战争的新希望
You can see that's the new hope for this war
有了新型战甲技术和很少的训练
With the new jack in technology and limited amount of training
瑞塔・沃塔斯基一天就可以杀掉
Rita Vrataski was able to kill hundreds of Mimics
几百个模仿者外星人
She was able to kill hundreds of Mimics on only her first day in combat.
如果全军都是这样的战士
Imagine any army of Rita Vrataski's.
我们在英吉利海峡抵挡住它们
We're managing to hold them back at the English Channel
问题是能挡多久?这种观点过于轻率
- but for how long? - It is a dangerous task
难免人们对此持怀疑态度
and it's easy to understand why people are so suspicious about this
超过70个国家加入了联合防御部队
Over seventy nations are joining the United Defense Force
以期将其击退  一劳永逸
which hopes to push them back once and for all.
我们控制住了局面
We've got 'em contained
有了这项新技术  绝对能打败它们
and with this new technology   we're gonna defeat 'em.
歼灭计划将会成为
Operation Downfall is going to be the largest
人类历史上规模最大的机甲战斗
mechanized invasion in the history of mankind.
我们一定会赢
We will be victorious.
因为我们会...
We fight.
和他们抗争到底
That's what we do.
(伦敦)
LONDON
我是威廉・凯奇少校
Major William Cage.
美国军方媒体的
United Stated military.
欢迎您来伦敦  少校
Welcome to London   Major.
(联合防御部队总部)
UNITED DEFENSE FORCE HEADQUARTERS
将军可以见你了
The General will see you now.
谢谢
Thank you.
行动计划是这样的
Operation Downfall
整个联合防御部队  从法国
the entire might of the UDF invading from France
地中海  斯勘的纳维亚直入
the Mediterranean   Scandinavia
缓解东部前线的压力
relieving pressure in the Eastern front and allowing
好让俄国和中国部队把敌人赶回去
the Russians and Chinese to push the enemy back
而全军在中部集合后
and we all meet in the middle
再一路把"拟态"(Mimics)斩尽杀绝
exterminating this Mimic scourge along the way.
很多优秀的战士明天会战死   少校
A lot of good soldiers are going to die tomorrow   Major
等硝烟散去...裹尸袋被送回来的时候
and when the smoke clears and the body bags start coming home
就会需要有个人来背黑锅
people tend to look for someone to blame
比如说   我
someone like me.
希望能有人为我说句公道话
Ideally I'd prefer a different scenario.
请吧
Please.
也许能写本畅销的回忆录?
A best selling memoir perhaps?
或者从此走上政坛?
Maybe a career in politics?
对我来说  马上想到的有...
Off the top of my head   I would go with the
"胸怀大志"
"The Sense of Manifest Destiny."
"白手起家却又平步青云"
"Rags to Riches: Rags Rise Through The Ranks."
"天生的领导者"
"Born to Deliver." You see people.
人们就喜欢听这类话题
Well   they'd love that sort of thing.
你理解错了  少校
You misunderstand   Major.
我不是请你推销我  而是推销这场反击战
I didn't ask you here to sell me   I want you to sell the invasion.
好的
Okay.
船一小时后出发
You ship out to the coast in one hour.
你的拍摄团队已经在等你了
Your comrade is standing by.
你们之后会去展开第一波攻击的海滩上
You'll be on the beach with the first wave.
抱歉...我问一下
I'm sorry.
第一波攻击将在海滩展开?
The first wave   the beach?
也就是说海滩将成为前线?
You mean  The front?
法国
France.
卫星显示海岸线上有极少量的敌人
Satellite show minimum enemy movement down the coast.
在做些许的抵抗
Little resistance.
到时应该会很精彩刺激
It'd be exciting
刺激到可以向子孙们说故事
something to tell your grandchildren.
很感激你对我的信心  将军
Well   I appreciate the confidence   General.
但我、我就是为了回避这种事情才只做现在这工作
I do  I do this to avoid doing that.
我、我、我在大学曾经是备役军官
I I  I was an ROTC in college
战争爆发后
and war broke out
我没了我的广告公司  所以我现在...
I lost my advertising firm and
才在这里做这种工作
here I am.
所以我有我的专长
I do what I do.
你...做你该做的事
You  you do what you do.
但...我真的不算当过兵
But  I'm not a soldier really.
对  你当然不是
No   of course you're not.
所以我才让你跟几十万士兵在一起
That's why I'm embedding you with several hundred thousand men and women who are.
我很荣幸   将军  但我承受不起
Well it is an honor   General. I'm afraid I'm gonna have to decline.
我是见血就晕
I can't stand the sight of blood
被纸割伤都受不了
not so much as a paper cut.
呃...不过
Uh  but
呃...既然话都说到这儿了
uh  it's sitting here thinking about this
我倒是有几个认识的人可以向你推荐一下
a couple of names come to mind that I feel like I could recommend to you inste
少校  这不是商量  是命令
It's not an offer   Major   it's an order.
将军  别忘了我是一名美国军官
General   I'm an officer in the United States Military.
你没权利命令我
You don't even have that authority
我跟你的长官说过了
I've spoken to your C.O.
你现在受我指挥
You are now under my command.
当然你还保留目前的军阶
You will retain your present rank of course.
我秘书会再跟你详谈
My secretary has all the details.
好好干吧   少校
Do a good job   Major.
祝你好运
Good luck.
你可以走了
Dismissed.
将军
General.
我已经鼓动了几百万人
I just inspired millions of people
加入你的军队
to join your army.
当裹尸袋被运送回国
And when the body bags come home
肯定要有个人出来背黑锅
and they're looking for someone to blame.
你觉得我该怎么写?才能让人们
How hard do you think it would be for me to convince people
不骂你?
to blame you?
我想将军也不想那样吧
I'd imagine a General would prefer to avoid that.
你是在威胁我吗  少校
Are you blackmailing me   Major?
我只是...
I would prefer
不想明天到海滩去拍摄那些勇士的英雄壮举
not to be filming acts of heroism and valor on that beach tomorrow.
你明天不用去了
You won't be.
很高兴能达成协议
I'm glad we could uh  work this out.
那将军  不介意的话  我先...
Now   if you'll excuse me   General   I
谢谢
Thank you.
把他抓起来
Arrest this man.
啊?
What?
不要跑!
Stop running!
航机将在10分钟后关门
Flight closing in 10 minutes.
站起来  废物
On your feet   maggot!
不许这样跟长官说话  中士
Now that's no way to address an officer   Sergeant.
我就是这样对待新兵的
That's how I address a slack-jawed recruit right
接着还会用鞋跟往新兵的屁眼塞
before I bust his hole with my boot heel.
废物
Maggot!
孩子  等等
Hold up there   son.
要帮忙吗?先生
Can I help you   sir?
中士  这里是哪里?
Where the hell am I   Sergeant?
希思罗前线指挥基地
Forward Operating Base   Heathrow.
你刚刚是跟新兵一起来的
You just came in with the fresh recruits.
我看着像新兵吗?
Do I strike you as a fresh recruit?
不  长官  你不像
No   sir   you do not.
我是威廉姆・凯奇少校  是美国军官
My name is Major William Cage   I'm an American officer
军官?
Officer?
这里是新兵营
This is Processing.
军官不会来这的  而却到这了  中士
There's no officers down here. I got this   Sergeant.
那你到底为什么会跑到新兵营来的?
How the hell did you end up in Processing?
怎么了?
What was it?
玩了一整晚的牌?单身派对?
Poker night? Bachelor party?
中士  若你不介意的话
If it's all the same to you   Sergeant.
我想跟华盛顿的指挥官解释一下
I'd like to explain that to my Commanding Officer in Washington.
如果你能告诉我电话在哪...
So if you just take me to the phone
你不听说吗?
Haven't you heard?
战争随时都可能开始
We're t-minusing our whole S.H. out
我们要深入法国
we're fixing to invade France.
整个基地都封闭了  不准通电话  接或打都不行
This whole F.O.P is on lockdown   no calls   in or out.
你叫法雷尔?
You're name's Farell?
没错
That's right.
二等士官长法雷尔
Master Sergeant Farell.
二等士官长法雷尔  美国人
Master Sergeant Farell   you're an American.
不  我从肯塔基来的
No   sir. I'm from Kentucky.
好吧  好 看看我
Okay   well  Look at me.
再看看这里
And look at where I am.
我是被迫的
I've been railroaded.
很明显地我不该在这里
It's obvious   I don't belong here.
所以拜托了  士官长
So please   Sergeant.
想办法让我打个电话
There has to be a way I can make a phone call.
我会带你去的
I'll get you sorted out   sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
这边走
Right this way.
士官长  你住肯塔基的哪?
Where are you from in Kentucky   Sergeant?
一个叫科学山丘的小镇
Little town called Science Hill.
- 听过吗? - 现在听过了
- Heard of it? - I have now.
- 那你从哪来? - 新泽西州的蔓越莓镇
- How about you   where are you from? - Cranberry   New Jersey.
那边出产蔓越莓?
They grow our cranberries there   do they?
产番茄  我吃过最好吃的番茄
Tomatoes   best I've ever had.
那为什么叫蔓越莓镇?
Why do they called Cranberry then?
那为什么叫科学山丘?
Why do they call it Science Hill?
没问过  无所谓
Never asked   don't care.
你先请
After you.
你不是带我去打电话吗?士官长
You're not taking me to a phone   are you   Sergeant?
不  我不是
No   I'm not.
看来你说的话  只有你的名字是真的
Seems about the only honest thing you've said to me so far is your name.
这上面说你是个逃兵
Says here you're a deserter.
说你因为冒充美国军官而被抓
Says here you were caught impersonating an officer
说你会试图往外打电话
It says here you'd likely try to make an outside call
甚至还会威胁到行动的安全
even compromise security of this operation.
说你只要能逃避打仗  什么都干得出来
Anything to get out of combat duty tomorrow.
但这些都不会发生
But that's not gonna happen.
都不会的
Ever.
二等兵凯奇
Private Cage.
人言可畏
Rumor is a terrible thing.
不用等到晚上  这些人对你的看法就会达成一致
And not following these men   we'll all reach the same conclusion.
你是个满口谎言的懦夫
That you're a coward and a liar
把自己的生命看得比其他生物的还重要
putting your life above theirs.
不过你还有希望  二等兵
The good new is there's hope for you   Private.
那就是参加这场光荣的战争
Hope in the form of glorious combat
战争是伟大的救世主
battle is the great redeemer
也是一个大熔炉  能锤炼出真正的英雄
fire and crucible in which the only true heroes are forged.
战场上没有高低贵贱之分
The one place where all men truly share the same rank
无论你来的时候是什么样的废物
regardless of what kind of parasitic scum they were going in.
全队都听着
Squad!
这位是二等兵凯奇
This here is Private Cage.
二等兵凯奇
Private Cage.
J分队
J Squad.
那不是军官制服吗
Isn't that an Officer's uniform?
他可能只是在炫耀他的装扮
Or he's showing off us the cufflinks.
看来大家早上过得都非常充实
I see everyone is having a productive morning.
看到你们这水准的人让我倍感自豪
You know it gives me a swell of pride knowing soldiers of your
因为明天是你们去冲锋陷阵
caliber will be leading the charge tomorrow.
长矛之尖
Tip of the spear.
利剑之刃
Edge of the knife.
通通都用来刺屁股
Crack of my ass.
二等兵  基梅尔
Private Kimmel
我对在军营里赌博是什么观点
what is my view of gambling in the barracks?
你不喜欢  法雷尔士官长
Dislike it   Sergeant Farell.
南希  我为什么不喜欢
Nance   why do I dislike it?
这会鼓励大家靠运气取胜 而不是靠自身素质
Cause it maintains the notion that our fate is in hands other than our own.
在命运面前 我们永远不变的态度是什么
And what is my definitive position on the concept of fate?
全体告诉我
Chorus.
纪律严明  时刻准备 做命运的主人
Through readiness and discipline   we are masters of our fate.
你们也许会觉得这很荒唐
You might call that notion ironic
但相信我
but trust me
你们会理解的
you'll come around.
二等兵凯奇是个逃兵
Private Cage is a deserter.
我要你们每一个人亲自负责教导他
I'm making you all personally responsible for his deliverance.
明天早上6点  他必须进入备战状态
He will be combat ready at 06:00 tomorrow.
备战状态?
Combat ready?
二等兵凯奇  他幻想自己不属于这里
Private Cage is under the delusion that he does not belong here
我们必须制止他的这种幻想
we must dissuade him of this delusion.
如果他试图逃跑
If he tries to run
你们可以随便揍他  揍到他没法站着撒尿
feel free dissuade him until he can't piss standing up.
士官长  你听我说
You have to listen to me
我不可能在这备战
I will never be combat ready
我嫉妒你  凯奇
I envy you   Cage.
明天早上你将接受洗礼  重获新生
Tomorrow morning you will be baptized   born again.
体能训练十分钟
PT   ten minutes!
服装不对  二等兵
You're not in uniform  Private.
新的一天
It's a new day   people!
命运在召唤
Destiny calls.
这世界只要我们做一件事
The world expects only one thing from us
取得胜利
that we will win!
来吧!基梅尔  开工了
Come on   Kimmel! Let's have it!
天呀...基梅尔
Oh   for Christ's sakes   Kimmel!
这样多自在
I gotta be free   man!
好了  上场了  我得穿的正式点
Alright   man. Let's get this show on the road   I gotta suite up.
那是什么鬼声音
What's that noise? That
我们走吧
Let's go!
拜托  先生
Listen   man!
我真的不是跟他们一伙的
I've never been in one of these.
是啊  我以前从来没玩过3P呢
Yeah   well   I've never been with two girls at the same time before.
如果你能帮我找两个女人来  我绝对能搞定
But you can bet when that day comes   I'll make it work.
呃...基梅尔?
Uh  Kimmel?
我叫格瑞夫
It's Griff.
格瑞夫、格瑞夫  你听我说
Griff. Griff   listen to me.
你想想
Think about this   man.
我可能会伤到别人
I could hurt somebody.
枪有保险装置的
Not with the safety on your one.
啊?
What?
保险装置在哪?
Where is the safety?
这就对了
Exactly!
(严禁穿越)
DO NOT CROSS
是时间了
It's time.
我的天呀!是钢筋铁骨娘
Bloody hell! It's the full metal
动起来!
Move!
- 格瑞夫 - 士官长?
- Griff. - Serge?
照顾一下二等兵凯奇
Take care of Private Cage!
什么?一整天吗?
What   all day?
我有预感  他撑不了一整天
Something tells me he won't be needing it that long.
格瑞夫
Griff!
凯奇
Cage!
我们丢了德国
We lost Germany.
又丢了法国
We lost France.
今天再输  那就没必要再打了
If we lose today we won't get to fight in battle.
我知道你们的压力很大
Now I know the pressure on you is enormous.
2分钟后空降
Two minutes to drop.
害怕是正常的
It's alright to be scared..
记着  没有恐惧就没有勇气
Remember   there's no courage without fear.
嘿
Hey!
喔  同学
Oy   mate!
你的衣服好像不太对劲
I think there's something wrong with his suite!
是啊
Yeah!
里面装着死人
There's a dead guy in it.
出去后可要小心你背后  先生
Hey   watch your back out there   sir.
没人会在你后面罩你的
No one else will.
1分钟
One minute!
1分钟后空降
One minute to drop!
喂
Hey!
怎么了
What?
告诉我怎么打开武器上的保险
How do I turn the safety off of my weapon?
什么
What?
怎么打开武器上的保险
How do I turn the safety off
我的天呀
Oh   my God!
全体准备
Everybody!
30秒后空降
Thirty seconds to drop!
听我指令
On my mark!
做好空降准备
Standby to deploy!
拉动空降索
Activate drop ride!
记着...
Remember
跳了!跳了!
Drop! Drop!
跳了!上了!
Drop! Go!
上了!上了!
Let's go! Let's go!
跳了!跳了!
Drop! Drop!
凯奇  不跳会死的!
Cage   drop or die!
耶!呜呼!
Yeah! Wooh!
我们成功了!
We made it!
队员们!我们成功了!耶...
Squad   we made it! Yeah
发生什...
What the ?!
二等兵凯奇
Private Cage!
你走错方向了
You're going the wrong way!
你会错过机会
You're gonna miss your moment!
这什么鬼地狱
What the hell?
它们不应该知道我们来
They're not supposed to know we're even coming.
老兄  我们进了屠宰场
It's a slaughter house   man!
是个屠宰场!
It's a slaughter house!
冷静点  福特
Pull yourself together   Ford!
全员  都起来
On your feet   people!
整队
Get in line!
南希!给我敌人的位置
Nance   get me a sitrep!
保险装置?
Safety?
格瑞夫、福特  到前面去
Griff   Ford   go to the front!
我的保险装置?
My safety?
要怎么打开枪的保险...?
How do I get my safety ?
我在等你呀!南希!
I'm waiting   Nance!
找到位置了!500公尺外  快速接近中
I got traces! Five hundred meters and they're coming in fast!
他妈贱货
Son of a bitch.
如果想待在那条上  就把阵行排好
Put a line if you want to stay that way.
待在各自的攻击位置
On your position!
开始行动
Move!
他们来了
Here they come.
来势汹汹  数量多的惊人
Mean as hell and filthy as grass.
等他们再靠近点
Wait till the other ride's on us!
再几秒
Few more seconds!
喂
Hey!
退后
Fall back!
重新装弹
Reload!
站起来  废物
On your feet   maggot!
在我用鞋跟塞你屁眼前  快列队!废物
Get in line before I bust your hole with my boot heel   maggot!
孩子  先等等
Hold up there   son.
要帮忙吗?先生
Can I help you   sir?
法雷尔士官长
Sergeant Farell
没错  就是我
That is my name.
我知道怎么回事了
I think I get it.
怎么了?
What was it?
打了一整晚的牌?
Poker night?
单身派对?
Bachelor party?
我也不知道
I'm not sure.
常有的事
It happens.
我会为你带路的  先生
I'll get you sorted out   sir.
我帮你拿
Let me take those for you.
今天...是什么日子
What  what day is it?
对你而言...
For you
是审判日
Judgment day.
好消息是你还有希望  二等兵
The good new is there's hope for your   Private.
那就是参加这场光荣的战斗
Hope in the form of glorious combat
战争是伟大的救世主
battle is the great redeemer
是一个大熔炉
the fire and crucible
能锤炼出真正的...
in which the only true heroes
能锤炼出真正的英雄
In which the only true heroes are forged.
你刚刚是不是打断我的话了  二等兵?
Did you just interrupt me   Private?
士官长
Sergeant.
你肯定不会相信我待会要跟你说的事情
You're  you're not gonna believe what I'm about to tell you.
不  我不信
No   I'm not.
刚才说到哪儿了
Now   where was I?
一个大熔炉
The Fire and crucible.
一个大熔炉...
The Fire and crucible
能锤炼出真正的英雄
in which the only true heroes are forged.
战场上没有高低贵贱之分
The one place where all men truly share the same rank
无论你来的时候是什么样的废物
regardless of what kind of parasitic scum they were going in.
小队!这位是二等兵凯奇
Squad! This here is Private Cage.
二等兵凯奇  这是J小队
Private Cage. J Squad.
那不是军官制服吗
Isn't that an Officers uniform?
他可能只是穿来炫耀他的衣服
He's showing off us the cufflinks.
要知道  看到你们这批水准的人让我倍感自豪
You know it gives me a swell of pride knowing soldiers of your
因为明天是你们去冲锋陷阵
caliber will be leading the charge tomorrow.
长矛之尖
Tip of the spear.
利剑之刃
Edge of the knife.
通通都是拿去刺屁屁的
Crack of my ass.
二等兵基梅尔  我对在军营里赌博是什么观点?
Private Kimmel   what is my view of gambling in the barracks?
你不喜欢  法莱尔士官长
Dislike it   Sergeant Farell.
南希  我为什么不喜欢?
Nance   why do I dislike it?
这会鼓励大家靠运气取胜 而不是靠自身素质
Cause it maintains the notion that our fate is in hands other than our own.
在命运面前  我们永远不变的是什么
And what is my definitive position on the concept of fate?
全体告诉我
Chorus.
纪律严明  时刻准备 做命运的主人
Through readiness and discipline we are masters of our fate.
你们也许会觉得这很荒唐
You might call that notion ironic
但相信我
but trust me.
你们会理解的
You'll come around.
我的天呀  基梅尔
Oh   for Christ's sakes   Kimmel!
这样多自在
I gotta be free   man!
好了  上场了  我得穿的正式点
Alright   man. Let's get this show on the road   I gotta suite up.
(开启状态)
Disengage.
老兄你在搞什么
Hey   what the hell's wrong with you   man?
难道你以前没穿过这个?
Haven't you been in one of these before?
也许吧
Maybe.
知道保险装置在哪吗
Do you know where the safety is?
不太清楚
I'm not sure.
很好
Good.
我知道你们的压力很大
Now I know the pressure on you is enormous.
2分钟后空降
Two minutes to drop.
害怕是很正常的
It's alright to be scared.
记住  没有恐惧  就没有勇气
Remember   there's no courage without fear.
同学
Hey   Oy   mate!
你的衣服好像不太对劲
I think there's something wrong with your suite!
是啊
Yeah!
里面装的是死人
There's a dead guy in it.
出去后可要小心后面
Hey   watch your back out there   sir.
没人会在后面罩你
No one else will.
吉茵珂丝  母狗一条
Jinx   bitch!
听我指令
On my mark!
做好空降准备
Standby to deploy!
拉动空降索
Activate drop ride!
30秒后空降
Thirty seconds!
- 要记住 - 喂
- Remember  - Hey!
耶!呜呼!我们成功了
Yeah! Wooh! We made it!
你后面
Behind you!
注意
Watch out!
来了
Incoming!
我中弹了
I'm hit!
很严重吗
How bad is it?
这里...是不是流了很多血?
Is there  a lot of blood?
你胸口有一个洞
You have a hole in your chest.
真假?
Really?
对
Yeah.
你刚刚拿走我的...我的电池...电池?
Did you just take my  my battery  battery?
噢  干  干!
Oh   no   no!
干你老...!?
Holy fuc !?
站起来  废物
On your feet   maggot!
法雷尔士官长
Sergeant Farell!
有什么事吗?先生
Can I help you   sir?
我是威廉姆・凯奇少校
My name is Major Will Cage.
美军媒体专员
U.S. Army Media Relations.
我没打一整晚的牌也没参加单身派对
I wasn't at a bachelor party or a poker game!
你的左侧口袋里有一封传令
You have an order in your left pocket
说我是个逃兵  因为冒充军官被抓
that says that I'm a deserter impersonating an officer.
但是上面并没说
But what it doesn't say is that your
你是来自肯塔基的科学山丘镇 二等士官长法雷尔
Your name is Master Sergeant Farell from Science Hill   Kentucky.
如果你给我半分钟时间解释
And if you'll give me thirty seconds to explain how I know
你就有可能救下这个基地里的所有士兵
that you may just save the lives of every soldier on this base.
你一定要听我说  敌人知道我们的计划
You have to listen to me! They know we're coming!
正等着我们
They're waiting for us!
我去过了
I have been there!
我看过了
I've seen it!
你门全部都会死
You're all doomed!
你门全都会死
You're doomed!
好  我冷静了
Okay   I'm calm.
好  没事了  我没事了
Okay   I'm fine. I'm fine.
是J小分队  对吗?
This is J Squad   yes?
对  是J小分队
This is J Squad   yes.
不相信我是吧?没关系
Not that I should know that   but okay.
你们有人曾见过我吗
Have any of you met me before?
贱货  我根本不认识你
Bitch   I don't know you.
这就对了  没错
Exactly! Yes!
谢谢
Thank you.
你叫南希
Your name is Nance.
你是比梅...凯梅!基梅尔!
You're Bimmel  Kimmel! Kimmel!
光屁股穿战甲  好自在
You fight balls out   literally.
福特
Ford.
斯金纳
Skinner.
格瑞夫
Griff.
你是...
You're
他不爱说话
He doesn't talk much.
这床底下藏着一副牌
But there's a card game under the bed
谢谢喔 屁眼人
Thanks a lot   asshole.
基梅尔是一副同花顺
Uh  Kimmel's winning on a flush.
是梅花、是方块
Uh  spades   no clubs.
你正打算收拾他们  我没说错吧
And you're gonna make them eat those cards. Am I right?
我待会要说的话  听上去很像是疯了
Now   what I'm about to tell you sounds crazy.
但是  是真的
It's true.
你们一定要听我说
And you have to listen to me.
这对你们来说很重要
You're very lives depend on it.
1分钟
1 minute!
他在说什么
What is he saying?
南希
Nance!
他在说什么
What is he saying?
听我指令
On my mark!
做好空降准备
Standby to deploy!
启动降落装置  30秒!
Activate drop ride   thirty seconds!..
这载运机要爆...
This ship is about to explo !
(开启)
Disengage.
耶!呜呼!我们成功了
Yeah! Wooh! We made it!
队员们!我们成功了
Squad   we made it!
别等我把鞋跟塞进你屁眼
Or I'll bust your hole with my boot heel!
耶!我们成功了
We made it!
队员们!我们成功了
Squad   we made it!
抱歉
I'm sorry!
我是在救你
I'm trying to save you.
这就是屠杀场
We're getting slaughtered.
你得把我们从海滩上弄走
You need to get us off this beach.
该离开了  这载运机马上就会爆炸
We have to go. This drop ship is about to explode.
该离开了  现在!
We have to go now!
等等
Wait.
快呀!
Come on!
快!
载运机马上要爆炸了
This ship is going to explode!
你在干什么
What are you doing?
醒了以后来找我
Find me when you wake up.
什么
What?
等你苏醒后来找我
Come find me when you wake up
站起来废物
On your feet   maggot!
在我把鞋跟塞进你屁眼之前快列队  废物
Get in line before I bust your hole with my boot heel   maggot!
好消息是你还有希望  二等兵
The good new is there's hope for your   Private.
战争是伟大的救世主
Battle is the great redeemer.
也是一个大熔炉 能锤炼出真正的英雄
Te fire and crucible in which the only true heroes are forged.
战场上没有高低贵贱之分
The one place where all men truly share the
小队  这位是二等兵凯奇
Squad this here is  Private Cage.
你们都是J小分队的
You must me J Squad.
幸会了各位
It's good to meet you.
那不是军官制服吗
Isn't that an officer's uniform?
- 他应该不是想炫耀... - 不是想炫耀...
- These sure ain't officers  - These sure ain't officers
这件衣服
cufflinks.
钥匙
Keys.
在左边口袋  大概吧
In the left pocket  Probably.
二等兵凯奇是个逃兵
Private Cage is a deserter.
我要你们每一个人亲自负责教导他
I'm making you all personally responsible for his deliverance.
明天早上6点 他必须进入备战状态
He will be combat ready by 06:00 tomorrow.
二等兵凯奇  他会幻想自己不属于这里
Private Cage is under the delusion that he does not belong here.
我们必须制止他的这种幻想
We must dissuade him of this delusion.
如果他试图逃跑  你们可以揍他
If he tries to run   feel free dissuade him until
喔  不、不、不、不  我...
Oh   no   no   no   no. I'm
我绝对不会离开你们的
I'm not gonna run from you guys.
- 呃...没机会逃跑的 - 揍到他没法站着撒尿
- It's uh  not a chance. - he can't piss standing up.
谢谢  法雷尔士官长
Thank you   Sergeant Farell.
那接下来呢  体能训练?
What next? A little uh  PT?
体能训练
PT!
十分钟
Ten minutes!
左
Left.
你们是干什么的
What do you stand up?
我们是战士
A warrior!
战士该干什么
What do warrior's do?
杀戮
Kill!
战士该干什么
What are you gonna do?
杀戮
Kill!
战士该干什么
What are you gonna do?
杀戮
Kill!
老兄  明天是我参加过的第20场战场
This is gonna be my twentieth battle tomorrow   man.
不可能有20场  老兄
You haven't been in twenty battles   man.
当然有
I have   too!
明天一到海滩  你肯定会吓傻的
You're gonna dump your load the second we hit the beach tomorrow.
拜托  你们俩能不能闭上臭嘴
Why don't you two get yourselves a nice hot cup of shut the hell up?
小妹你真幽默
You funny   girl.
我打赌明天我会破纪录
But I bet you I set some iron record tomorrow.
是掉头逃跑最快纪录吧
Busting his hand moving back when he falls forward
别踩到自己拉的屎
slipping in your shit.
别在那讲屁话
Knock off the grab ass!
闭嘴  士官长
Grab this   Serge!
停下来
Hold up!
二等兵 趴下做
Private give me
50个  是吗
Fifty   Serge?
没错
That's right.
50个
Fifty.
全排
Platoon.
给我做50个伏地挺身
Drop and give me fifty.
感谢二等兵凯奇
Compliments of Private Cage!
谢谢  中士
Thank you   Serge.
一
- And one! - One!
二
- And two! - Two!
三
- And three! - Three.
噢!这智障的脑子里到底装了些什么?
Oh! What the hell were you thinking?
你还有希望  二等兵
There's hope for your   Private.
那就是参加这场光荣的战斗
Hope in the form of glorious combat.
战争是伟大的救世主
Battle is the great redeemer.
二
Two.
三
Three.
(请勿穿越)
DO NOT CROSS
打扰一下  弗拉塔斯基中士
Excuse me   Sergeant Vrataski?
打扰一下
Excuse me.
弗拉塔斯基中士
Sergeant Vrataski?
打扰一下
Excuse me.
什么事
Ya?
谁让你跟我说话了
Yes! Who said you could talk to me?
我脸上有东西吗?
Have I got something on my face   soldier?
你干的  是你干的
You did. You did.
明天在海滩
Tomorrow   at the beach.
我们相遇
We meet.
你要我苏醒之后来找你
You said to find you when I wake up.
你肯定知道些什么
You do know what's happening to me.
跟我来
Come with me.
现在
Now.
否则  最好的结果是被关进精神病院
Cause the best case scenario is you're gonna end up in a psych ward.
最坏的结果  是被当试验品解剖
The worst case you'll get dissected for study.
明白了吗
Are we clear?
了解?
Yes?
了解
Yes.
第一次死是什么情况
First time you died   what happened?
你杀了个"拟态"(Mimics)
You killed a Mimic?
描述一下
Describe it.
很特别
Uh  it was different.
体型大
It was a bigger.
蓝色的
Blueish.
你被它的血液喷到了
And you got covered in its blood.
没错  被喷到了
As a matter of fact   I did.
它们事先知道了
They know we're coming.
所以明天在海滩
On the beach tomorrow.
是场屠杀
It's a slaughter   isn't it?
你是怎么知道的
How do you know this?
你能不能  等等
Could you just  Wait!
等等
Wait! Wait!
能不能请你跟我解释一下
Would you please just explain to me what the hell is happening?
这到底是怎么回事
What happened to you happened to me.
我曾经也经历过  但后来又没了  就这样
I had it   I lost it. Okay?
你这样挺好的  所以有治疗方案  我怎么摆脱这个?
I mean   that's great   there's a cure. How do I get rid of this?
我需要你的帮助
First I need your help.
我能怎么帮你
Help with what exactly?
打赢战争
Winning the war.
跟我来  快
Let's go   come on!
瑞塔  什么意思
Rita   what is this?
瑞塔  你来这儿干什么?你该先告诉我的
Rita   what are you doing here? You've got to give me some warning.
他是谁
Who's this?
他就是有我在凡尔登之前遇到的现象的人
He's me   before Verdun.
他会帮我们的
He's gonna help us.
什、你说他是
What   you mean   he's ?
对
Yes.
- 什么时候死的?在哪? - 在沙滩  明天
- When did he die? Where? - On the beach   tomorrow.
我在背后竖起了几根手指
How many fingers am I holding up behind my back?
我怎么会知道
How should I know that?
好吧
Okay.
这是我们第一次这样对话
So this is the first time we've had this conversation?
给他试试这个
We should try this on him?
- 这是什么鬼东西 - 没用的
- What the hell is that? - It doesn't work.
- 他看见什么了吗? - 什么看见
- Has he had any visions yet? - Visions of what?
还得需要点时间
Okay   so there's still time.
- 是的 - 时间?等等  抱歉
- Yes. - Time? Look   I  I'm sorry.
他是谁
What  who is this?
你是谁
Who are you?
我是卡特博士
I'm Dr. Carter.
粒子物理高等微生物学
Particle Physics Advanced Microbiology.
他是唯一相信你经历的人
He's also the only other person who'll believe what's happening to you.
没人比他更了解模仿者外星人
No one understands Mimic biology   better than him.
他是白宫的首席分析师
He's a top analyst at the Whitehall.
那已经是遇见瑞塔之前的事了 现在我只是个
Ye  well   I mean   I was until I met Rita and now I'm just a a
精神有问题的机械师
"mechanic with psychiatric delusions."
卡特  给他看看
Carter   show him.
好  首先  你不是在跟军队作战
Right   the first of all   you're not fighting an army.
你得把它想成是一个单独的生物体
You have to think of this as a single organism.
看  这些触手让它们行动非常灵活
Now these common drones   they act like its claws.
α  就是你杀死的那种  数量没那么多
That Alpha's   like the one that you killed   are much more rare.
我估计618万才会有一只
Yeah   they're like one in six point one eight million   by my guess.
它们会预知敌人的行动
They act as the enemies
就像中枢神经系统一样
They're like its central nervous system.
而这个  就是大脑
But this  is the brain.
它们的指挥部
It controls them all.
它就是Ω
And this is the Omega.
它有一种控制时间的能力
And the Omega has the ability to control time.
一但α被杀
Whenever an Alpha is killed
一种自动反应就会被触发
an automatic response is triggered.
Ω就会重启当天
The Omega starts the day over again.
它会记住即将发生的事
But you see this time it can remember what's going to happen
就像你一样
just like you do.
在我们行动之前  它会预知我们要干什么
It-it knows exactly what we're going to do before we're gonna do it.
能预知未来的敌人  很难战胜
And an enemy that knows the future can't lose.
如果这样  凡尔登那次是怎么赢的
But if that's true   how did you win in Verdun?
是对方故意的让我们赢的
We were allowed to win.
它想让我们相信  我们能赢
This thing wants us to believe we can win.
诱使我们不惜一切代价投入这场战争
It wants us to throw everything we have into the invasion.
其实这场战争  不是我们的收官之战
Operation Downfall isn't our end game.
而是敌人的
It's the enemy's.
要明白  这是一种
The thing you've got to understand is this is a
经过完美进化的霸主级生物
perfectly evolved world conquering organism.
能想像成  会有成千上万的这样的东西
For all we know   there are thousands   millions   of those asteroids
漂浮在宇宙中  就像病毒一样
floating around the cosmos like a virus.
它们就等着在合适的条件下登入地球
And it's just waiting to crash land into a world with just the right conditions.
最终目的是攻击地球上的人类  然后
All they need is for the dominant life form to attack and
它们会横扫一切  统治整个地球
And they'll be nothing to stop the Mimics from conquering the rest of the world.
除非你阻挡它们
Unless you change the outcome.
我?
Me?
你杀掉阿尔法的时候
When you killed that Alpha   you inadvertently
无意中进入了敌人的神经系统
entered the enemy's nervous system.
凯奇
Cage.
你掌握了它控制时间的能力  可以随时重启当天
You've seized control of the Omega's ability to reset the day.
这怎么可能
How is that even possible?
这东西唯一的弱点
Perhaps this organism's only vulnerability
对付它最有效的手段  就是人性
its  its only vulnerability  is humanity.
不管怎么样  你拥有了这个能力
Regardless of that   you control the power now.
就像当初我在凡尔登时一样
Just as I did in Verdun.
所以我能重启时间
So I'm resetting the day?
好
Okay.
需要怎么操控这能力
How do I control it?
你必须死
You have to die.
天天死
Every day.
直到Ω被摧毁
Until the Omega is destroyed.
首先  你的演示很精彩
Fist of all   that was a terrific presentation.
非常完美
Terrific.
我认识将军
I know the General.
我们应该向他汇报
We should take this to him.
告诉将军你们说的这一切  而不是...
You just tell him everything you told me   he would know
我去见过将军  凯奇
I went to see the General   Cage.
而且是无数次
Many number of times.
精神病院、解剖研究
Psyche ward   dissection.
记得吗
Remember?
那你们希望我怎么做
What are you expecting from me?
你有没有看到什么异象
Have you seen anything strange?
你在开玩笑吗
Is he shitting me?
幻象
Visions.
幻象!你看见过这样的幻象吗
Visions! Have you seen any visions like that?
Ω对力量失去控制会有感知
The Omega centers when its losing control of its power.
现在它一直在用精神力量搜寻你
Even now its mentally searching to find you.
一旦你快被找到时  就会产生各种幻象
When its close to finding you   you will start having visions.
你就会看见它
You'll start to see that.
甚至能看到它在哪
You'll even see where it is.
你也看过幻象
And you had these visions?
是的
Yes.
你亲眼见过它  真的看过  对吗
But eventually you saw it   I mean   you actually saw it. Right?
我从没见过它
Never in the flesh.
那这一切都只是些
So this is all just some
理论?
theory?
你们无法确定这些事情是确实存在的
You don't know if this thing even exists.
幻象告诉我  它就在凡尔登
The visions showed me it was at Verdun.
我看过了
I could see it!
我...我只是
I I just
在找到它之前失去了这种能力
lost the power before I could get to it.
等我们拿下凡尔登
And by the time we took Verdun
Ω早跑了
the Omega was gone.
好  那我要做的就是等待这些幻象
Okay   so all I have to do is wait to have these visions
然后再告诉你们这家伙在哪儿
and then tell you where this Omega thing is?
不  凯奇
No   Cage.
你要带我去那
You're gonna get me there
由我来干掉它
and I'm gonna kill it.
带你去?
Get you there?
我根本没接受过战斗训练
I mean   I'm not even trained for combat.
重新装弹
Reload.
没事吧  凯奇
You alright   Cage?
好像哪儿摔断了
I think I broke something.
哪?
What?
我的背
My back.
我现在只能感觉到嘴唇
The only thing I can feel are my lips.
你仔细听好了  这是条很重要的规则
Now listen carefully. This is a very important rule.
也是唯一的规则
This is the only rule.
如果在战斗中受伤  你要保证自己死去
You get injured on the field   you better make sure you die.
为什么
Why?
上次我在战斗中被击中了
Last time I was in combat   I was hit.
当时失血很多  差点儿就死了
I was bleeding out   just not fast enough.
输了三袋血后  我在战地医院苏醒过来
I woke up in a field hospital with three pints of someone else's blood
人已经废了
and I was out.
失去了那种能力  你明白吗?
I lost the power   do you understand?
所以再来一遍吧?
Then you better start over   don't you?
什么
What?
没人知道二等兵凯奇怎么了
No one knows what happened to Private Cage?
斯金纳你这笨蛋  他就在你旁边
Skinner   you dumb ass   he was right next to you
别告诉我你不知道那家伙跑哪去了
you're telling me you don't know where that slippery son of a bitch went?
不  中士
No   Serge!
好吧
Alright.
那就再来50个  怎么样?
- Let's do another fifty   shall we? - Oh   no!
一
And one!
不  等等
No! Wait   wait!
我叫威廉姆・凯奇
My name is Will Cage.
我们在沙滩见过
I we met on the beach.
是将在沙滩见  明天
We meet on the beach   tomorrow.
我们是一类人
I have what you had.
好了  再来一遍
Alright   let's go again.
你没有时间多想
You don't have time to think.
记住  光知道它们的位置还不够
Remember   it's now enough knowing where they're going to be
必须知道怎么杀掉它们
you have to know how to kill them.
好的...等等!等等!
That's it  hold on! Hold on!
听我说!听我说!
Listen! Listen!
好吧  动手吧
Okay   do it.
站起来  废物
On your feet   maggot!
停
Stop!
等等等等
Wait   wait   wait   wait!
停下来!等!等一下
Stop! Wait! Wait a second!
等一下
Wait a second!
我一直在想
You know   I've been thinking.
这东西在我的血液里
I mean   this thing's in my blood.
也许有什么办法  我可以把它传给你
So maybe there's some way I can transfer it to you.
我试过了  跟本不行
I've tried everything   it doesn't work.
你有没有...
And have you
你知道的
You know?
试过所有的可能性
Tried all  all the options?
喔  你想说做爱?
Oh   you mean sex?
对  试过了
Yep   tried it.
试过几次
How many times?
行了
Alright.
左边  左边  左边  左边
Left   left   left   left!
睁大你的眼睛
Keep your eyes open.
再来
Again!
等等  我觉得可以了
Just wait   wait! I think I'm okay.
站起来  废物
On your feet   maggot! Maggot! Maggot!
我已经很客气了  废物!快动起来
Now   I'm done being nice to you   maggot! Now move!
你没事吧?凯奇
You okay   Cage?
喔  没事没事  我很好
Oh   yeah! Yeah   I'm good! I'm good!
你的腿断了
You're leg's broken.
没这回事  我还能感觉到脚趾
No! I  I can still feel my toes.
噢...不是吧
Oh   come on!
瑞塔  这什么意思?你来这干什么?你该先告诉我的
Rita! Rita! What is this? What are you doing here?
他是谁
Look   who's this guy?
- 他就是我有凡尔登之前的 - 有凡尔登之前的
- He's me  before Verdun. - before Verdun.
什么?你是说他是
What  what do you mean? He's ?
对
Yes! Yes!
什么时候死的?在哪?
When did he die? Where?
在沙滩  明天
On the beach   tomorrow.
我是威廉姆・凯奇  你是卡特博士
I'm Will Cage   you're Dr. Carter.
我们曾有这次对话  你在背后竖起两根手指
We've had this conversation before. You have two fingers behind your back.
我看过幻象
I've had the visions.
见过Ω了
I've seen the Omega.
我们明天会败得很惨
It's  pretty much game over tomorrow
所以我们可以不必在这浪费时间了
So can we move this along?
好吧
Okay.
在哪儿
Where?
那有水坝  在山里
There's a dam   it's in the mountains.
我看见了德文标识
I saw German writing.
你能找到它的位置吗
Do you think you can work out where that is?
Well   I mean there can't be too many places that fit that
description. Do you think you can work out where that is?
我觉得你说的那种地方不会太多
Well   I mean there can't be too many places that fit that description.
我来试试吧
I'll see what I can do.
训练结束了
Training's over.
我们明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
- 我们还不知道去哪儿 - 很快就会知道了
- We don't even know where we're going. - We will   soon enough.
你现在要想想  怎么在海滩上保住命
In the mean time   you need to figure out a way to get us off that beach.
然后呢?我们去哪
What next? Where are we going?
哪条路  快想
- Yeah  - Which way? Focus!
哪条路
Which way?
我在想  我在想
I'm thinking. I'm thinking.
好...噢干!
Okay  Oh   man!
我们走了多远
How far do we make it?
这真的很难说
Well   it's  hard to say.
等等
Hold!
好  走
Okay   go!
他妈贱货
Son of a bitch!
- 我想是往左挪步、躲避 - 好
- I thought stepping left   ducking. - Fine.
说清楚  往左挪步
Just for the record   stepping left
- 往左挪步、往右躲避 - 已经很具体了
- Stepping left   ducking right. - It was pretty specific.
往左挪步  往右躲避
Stepping left   ducking right.
继续
Move on.
等等
Hold on!
现在记住  要穿过战壕  正前方
Now remember   across the trench   twelve o'clock
注意你的右侧
then look to your right.
还是不够具体?明白吗?
You're not being specific   you understand?
好
Oh   okay.
必须要非常具体  否则我死定了
You need to be specific   otherwise I'm dead.
瑞塔
Rita.
凯奇
Cage!
一步一步走到战壕的顶端
That takes us up to the top and then the trench.
向左挪步  那有"拟态"(Mimics)
I'm gonna step left   there's gonna be a Mimic there which
我会杀掉它
I'll kill
载运机爆炸  我要向西北前进30步
There's an explosion   I'm gonna run thirty paces to the north west.
到达战壕顶端时要蹲下  然后应该向左转
I'm gonna duck at the top of that trench   and then I'm gonna turn left.
我脸上有东西吗
I got something on my face?
没有
No!
凯奇
Cage!
我们在到处找你
We've been looking everywhere for you!
凯奇
Cage!
大家
Guys.
大家  今天
Guys can we just
就歇一歇吧
not do this today?
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
因为找不到你  法雷尔都快把我们折磨死了
Farell almost strung us up by our bullocks for losing track of you!
好了  斯金纳
Okay   Skinner.
你看着
Watch this.
现在我闭上眼睛
Now I'm gonna close my eyes.
- 好了 - 是的
- Ready? - Yeah.
我一点都没埋怨你
I didn't mind the extra push ups.
新的一天
It's a new day   people!
命运在召唤
Destiny calls.
这世界只要我们做一件事
The world expects only one thing from us:
取得胜利
That we will win!
从前线传回的战况  联合防御部队伤亡惨重
The current situation on the front line show heavy casualties
是时候让那些东西看看我们的实力了
It's about time we showed those things what we're made of.
我父亲可是不列颠战争中的飞行员
My father flew in the battle of Britain
美国人是三年后才参战的
three years before the yanks came into the war.
我们势不可挡  绝对有种
Couldn't be broken   backbone.
我叔叔乔治参加过诺曼地登陆
My Uncle George landed on the beach of Normandy   yeah.
真的  让他们打  这仗我们早就拿下了
In their day   this war would have been over by now.
这些家伙到底想要什么
What do they want with us anyway?
这还用问吗?矿产
It's obvious   isn't it? Minerals.
矿产
Minerals?
- 对  金属矿产 - 他们要的是氧气
- Yeah   minerals. - Oxygen   they want.
这有什么区别
What difference does it make?
他们来了  也赢了
They're here   they're winning.
无论想要什么  都会得到的
And whatever it is   they're gonna get it.
你不是该去那吗
Shouldn't you be over there?
我早去过了
I've been over there.
比谁去的次数都多
More times than anybody.
不怕告诉你们  我已经死过很多次了
As a matter of fact   I'm usually long dead by now.
懦夫
Coward.
怎么回事?停电了
- What's going on? - The power's gone.
我找到Ω了  它一定在这
I found the Omega. I found it. It has to be here.
德国卡内拉大坝  肯定是这儿
Groser Dam   Germany. This as got to be it.
跟描述完全一致
It fits the description perfectly.
是  你找到了
Yes   you found it.
又一次地
Again.
那又能怎么样?我们根本到不了那
What difference does it make? Cause we're never gonna get there.
不管我们怎么做
No matter what we do
不管我们怎么精心策划
no matter how carefully we plan
都过不了海滩那一关
we can't get off that beach.
你能做到的  你能
You can do this. You can.
你每天都到这来  我来训练你
You keep coming here everyday and I'll train you.
已经训练过了
You already have.
我在等你呀!南希
I'm waiting   Nance!
50公尺外快速接近中
Five hundred meters and closing fast!
怎么回事
What the ?!
重新装弹
Reloading.
接着怎么做
What's next?
一直向前
Straight shot.
到山那儿
Up the hill.
好
Okay.
中士
Hey   Serge.
新来那家伙
The new guy
他叫什么来着
what's his name again?
得有交通工具才能深入到内陆
We need a vehicle to get further inland.
有什么问题吗
Then what's the problem?
问题是那里肯定有伏击
The problem is the ambush waiting for us down
还没找到车就会被杀掉
there   they kill before we find a working car.
好  那现在怎么办
Okay   so what's the current plan?
还有两辆车可以试试  小型货车
The two cars I haven't tried are the Minivan
好
Yep.
- 和绿色越野车 - 好
- And the green SUV. - Okay.
我去找越野车  把"拟态"(Mimics)引过去
I'll head for the SUV   draw the Mimics to me
你去找小型货车
You go for the Minivan.
发动之后就直接开走
You get it started   just go   take off.
-   不用等我 - 好
- Do not wait for me. - Okay.
对了  发动前一定别忘了把拖车解开
Well  just don't forget to disconnect the caravan before you take off.
你要的是速度
You are going to be in a hurry
别拖着个累赘
you don't want any dead weight.
拜托
Come on.
快呀!凯奇
Come on   Cage!
我看不见
Can't see!
你能吗
Did you ?
政府提醒市民不要外出 保持镇定
Stay where you are   remain calm.
如果你在车里  请锁上车不要出来
If you are in a vehicle   please lock the doors and stay inside.
敌人已经到了伦敦
The enemy has reached London.
重复一遍
Repeat.
伦敦也受到了袭击
London is under attack.
车技不错
That's good driving.
我忘了解开拖车了
I forgot to unhook the trailer.
你不太爱说话
You don't talk much.
不喜欢说话
Not a fan.
说话
Of talking?
不太喜欢说话  对
Not a fan of talking   no.
不过  你还是跟我说了
You know   you eventually do talk to me.
你曾经跟我说过
It's usually around Lyon
你和你的家人一起去过里昂市
you tell me about the time you went there with your family.
你弟弟走丢了
Your brother got lost.
我从没去过里昂市
I've never been to Lyon.
还说过你的中间名
You tell me your middle name.
佩顿
Peyton.
那不是我的中间名
That's not my middle name.
你是在拱廊找到你弟弟的
You found your brother in the arcade   by the way.
那应该都是我胡编的  为了让你安静点
Well maybe I made it all up just to keep you quiet.
反正我们聊过
But you do talk to me.
凯奇  我没有必要去了解你
Cage   I do not need to get to know you.
如果你是聪明人  就别跟我打关系
And if you knew what was good for you   you wouldn't want to get to know me either.
多想想怎么保命吧
It's the only way you make it through this thing.
那你认识亨德里克吗
What about Hendricks   you get to know him?
你怎么知道这个名字
How do you know that name?
你说的
You mention him.
不可能
That's not possible.
- 不然我怎么知道 - 我什么时候说的
- Then how do I know his name? - When did I mention him?
在什么情况下
Under what circumstance?
因为他  你才不跟我说话
Is he why you won't talk to me?
最好别再提他的名字
Don't ever mention his name again.
为什么
Why
- 你爱他? - 他死了
- are you in love with him? - He's dead!
我亲眼看他死过300次
And I watched him die three hundred times
而且记得所有细节  记得任何事
and I remember  every detail   I remember everything.
所以我不想再谈这些
So I don't need to talk about it.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
战争就是这样
It's just war.
什么都没有  我们走吧
There's nothing here   keep going.
得先找到钥匙
We have to find the keys.
弄点儿油就行了
Let's just siphon the gas.
有飞机为什么还要开车
And why drive when we can fly?
这东西
In that thing?
我知道了  你肯定恐高
Let me guess   you're afraid of heights.
我是害怕坠机
I'm afraid of crashing.
这又没什么可丢人的
I'm not at all ashamed to admit it.
没事的  凯奇  能克服
You'll be fine   Cage. You'll learn.
- 怎么了 - 没什么  我没事
- What is it? - It's nothing   I'm fine.
- 怎么了 - 没什么
- What is it? - It's nothing.
瑞塔
Rita.
我看看
Let me see.
得找到直升机的钥匙
We have to find the keys to the helicopter.
肯定在附近什么地方
I'm sure they're around here somewhere.
直升机的油是满的
You know the heli's full of fuel
我找到一根软管
I found a hose.
用飞的  凯奇
We're flying   Cage.
你知道就算我们找到了钥匙
Well   let's just say we find keys   you know?
就算开走了那架直升机
Get that helicopter started.
我们既没有战甲  也没有弹药
We don't have our jackets or ammunition.
马上就要天黑了
And it's gonna be dark in a few hours.
我们还不如回到刚才那个农舍
Might be better just going back to the farmhouse
找点什么有用的  在那里过一夜
seeing what we could salvage. You know   spend the night there.
早上再回这儿
Come back here in the morning.
蜷缩在篝火旁边  再开上一瓶好酒
And curl up by the fire and open a bottle of wine?
我觉得我们还是应该重置
We should just reset.
- 这是死路一条 - 嘿  等  只是
- It's a dead end. - Hey   hold  just
如果你认为都没差的话
If it's all the same to you
我累了  我很痛苦  我宁可重新再来一次
I'm tired   I'm in pain. I'd rather just start fresh.
先休息一下 咖啡煮好了
I'll tell you what   take a few minutes. Coffee's ready.
我去找找钥匙  应该能找到
I'll look around for the keys   that's productive.
十分钟
Ten minutes.
好
Okay.
然后我杀掉你
And then I'm killing you.
好
Fine.
你居然能找到咖啡
I can't believe you found coffee.
谢谢
Thank you.
加糖  对吗
Oh. Sugar   right?
对
Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
等等  三勺
Hold on   three.
你喜欢加三勺
You like three.
那儿有件衬衣  你应该能穿
There's a shirt over there   it should be your size.
我们来这里几次了
How many times have we been here?
来过几次
How many times?
钥匙在哪
Where are the keys?
- 钥匙到底在哪 - 好
- Where are the Goddamn keys? - Okay.
你会开的  对吧
You can fly it   can't you?
不会...会
No. Well  yes.
我只会起飞  降落还没学会
I mean   I can take off   I'm still working on my landing.
那还在这里干什么?简直在浪费时间
What are we still doing here? You're wasting time!
瑞塔
Rita.
发动引擎你就会死
You start that engine   you die!
你最多只能活到这
This is as far as you go.
无论我做什么
No matter what I do.
你都会死在这里
This is as far as you ever make it.
20码以外藏着一个"拟态"(Mimics)
There's a Mimic buried twenty yards away.
你发动引擎  它就会攻击你
It attacks when you start the engine.
拿上你的武器上直升机  凯奇
Get your weapon and get in the helicopter   Cage.
回到那边会遇到更多
There's more than a field battle there.
我们俩只有一个能回去
Only one of us ever makes it.
上来
Get in.
唯一没有试过的方案就是
The only thing we haven't tried is a version where
你回去  回到农舍去
you walk away   just go back to the farmhouse.
有吃的  你在这儿等着我回来
There's food   you wait there until I get back.
你会安全的
You'll be safe.
我是士兵  我是自愿的
I'm a soldier   I volunteered.
我不会让开
I'm not walking away.
那你会死的
You die here!
死在这
Right here!
我救不了你
I can't save you.
而之后我若去杀了Ω
And if I go on and kill the Omega.
你的死
You're dead.
会成为既定事实
Forever.
我怎么样有那么重要吗
Why does it matter what happens to me?
我希望没见过你
I wish I didn't know you.
可是没办法
But I do.
我的中间名...
My middle name
是罗斯
is Rose.
站起来  废物
On your feet   maggot!
好消息是你还有希望  二等兵
Looks there's hope for your   Private.
那就是参加这场光荣的战斗
Hope in the form of glorious combat.
战争是伟大的救世主
Battle is the great redeemer.
也是一个大熔炉  能锤炼出真正的英雄
The fire and crucible in which the only true heroes are forged.
The one place
什么事
Yes?
谁让你跟我说话了
Who said you could talk to me?
难道我脸有东西吗?士兵
Do I have something on my face   soldier?
很抱歉打扰你了
I'm sorry to disturb you   Sergeant.
好了  上场了  我得穿得正式点儿
Alright   man. Let's get this show on the road. I gotta suite up.
你的头盔呢
Where's your helmet?
我不打算戴
I'm not gonna wear one.
很不方便
It's a distraction.
你喝酒了吧
Have you been drinking?
再给我三个556的弹簧夹
I need three more clips of five-five-six
八颗手雷  还有一块电池
eight grenades and an extra battery.
快点
Get it!
嘿
Oy!
同学
Oy   mate!
你的衣服好像不太对劲
I think there's something wrong with your suite!
里面装的是死人
There's a dead guy in it.
耶!
Yeah!
呜呼!我们成功了
Wooh-hoo! We made it!
感谢苍天  我们成功了!耶
Thank God   we made it! Yeah !
了结呀!
Finish it!
它不在那
It isn't there.
Ω不在那?
What do you mean the Omega isn't there?
我猜它从来就没在那儿
My guess is it never was.
它们知道我们要来
They knew we were coming.
它们伏击了我们  幻象就是个陷阱
They ambushed us. The visions were a trap.
就像瑞塔在凡尔登看到的幻象一样
Just like Rita's visions were a trap at Verdun.
它可以杀我但没杀
It could have killed me   but it didn't.
它想要我的血
It's after my blood.
那它们知道你是谁了
So they know who you are   they
它们想恢复能力
They want their power back.
就算这次没成  早晚也会
And they're gonna get it one way or another
除非我们能找到Ω
unless we find the Omega.
没别的办法了  我们完了
There  there isn't any other way   we're finished!
不  我们还没完
No   we're not finished.
那个没用  我无法让它工作
It doesn't work. I can't get it to work
你在白宫做过一个原型
You built a prototype at Whitehall.
没错  托你的福  我为此丢了工作
Yes! And I got fired for it   thank you very much.
- 这到底是什么东西 - 这是个转发器
- What is this thing   anyway? - It's a transponder.
把它放到α体内
You stick it into the Alpha and it taps into
它会跟Ω之间产生信息波段
the wavelength connecting it to the Omega.
这就是它的工作原理
That's the idea anyway.
但我没法让它工作  现有的设备根本不行
But I can't get it to work   not with the equipment I have on hand.
哪儿有你需要的设备
How do we get you what you need?
刚才她不是说了吗
Well   that's the thing. I mean
在白宫里的那个  差不多都可以进行测试了
when I was at Whitehall I built one   I was even ready to test it
我跟主管汇报以后
but when I told my superiors about it
就把工作丢了
well I lost my job.
都觉得他疯了
They thought he was crazy.
所以我们需要去趟白宫
So all we need to do is go to Whitehall.
等到接近大门  你就会被捕的
He'd be arrested ten feet from the front doors.
精神病院、解剖试验  记得吗
Psyche ward dissection   remember?
嘿、嘿、嘿!你们还忘了一件事
Hey   hey   hey! Aren't you forgetting something?
转发器要在活的α身上才管用
The transponder requires a live Alpha to make it work.
我们不需要
We don't need one.
我们有更好的选择
We got the next best thing.
等中国代表团出来时要加快脚步
When the Chinese delegation comes out   you pick up the pace.
那个戴黄袖章的家伙每次都能认出你
There's a guy with a yellow arm band that always recognizes you.
所以你要低着头  在我右边走
So just keep your head down and stay to my right.
干得不错
Nicely done.
三
Three.
二
Two.
一
One.
走
Go.
转身
Turn.
好的  继续走  眼睛往前看
Okay   keep walking. Just go straight ahead.
罗宾森
Robinson
我说过了别打扰我
I've asked not to be disturbed.
你最好有个好理由
This had better be critical.
人类的生死存亡
Fate of mankind.
这个理由够吗
Critical enough?
我不是活见鬼了吧
I don't believe what I'm seeing.
我已经见过很多次了
I've had more than my share of that.
坐下  将军  离那桌子远一点
Sit down   General   and stay away from your desk.
我要是你  就不会当儿戏
I'd take her very seriously if I were you.
真是让人佩服  少校
I have to hand it to you   Major.
你离开这间办公室的时候  从没想到你会回来
When you left this office today   I never imagined you'd be back
更别说是载誉归来的战斗英雄
let alone with my most decorated soldier.
我给你讲个故事吧  将军
I'm here to tell you a story   General.
一开始听着肯定会觉得很荒唐
And at first it's gonna sound ridiculous
但你越往下听
but the longer I talk the more rational
会越觉得合理
it's going to appear.
告诉他  一会打回去
Tell him you'll call back.
告诉谁
Tell who?
是博蒙特少校  从哈利法克斯打来的
Major General Beaumont calling from Halifax
他的飞机没能按时起飞
His plane's just been delayed.
天气不好
Bad weather.
你好
Yes?
谢谢  博蒙特  一会儿打给你
Thank you   Beaumont. I'll call you back.
明天的战斗是场屠杀
Tomorrow's invasion is a slaughter.
我到海滩上  不超过五分钟就会死
I'm dead within five minutes of landing on that beach
那些被你送上去的士兵也一样
along with every other soldier you are sending.
因为敌人早就知道我们的计划
And that's because the enemy knows we're coming.
我怎么知道的
Now how do I know this?
我临死前杀了一个"拟态"(Mimics)
Before I died I killed a Mimic
只是它有点特别
only this one was different.
它传了一些东西到我的血液里
It passed something onto me in my blood.
我能在同一天里周而复始地活着
Now I relive the same day over and over again.
就跟它们一样
Just like they do.
弗拉塔斯基中士在凡尔登也一样
Just like Sergeant Vrataski at Verdun.
告诉你的秘书  你这一切正常
Tell your secretary everything's fine.
你说什么
I beg your pardon?
我很抱歉  将军  不知道您有客人
Oh   I'm sorry   General. I thought you were alone.
没事
It's fine.
她打印好了文件等你签字
She typed up those orders for you to authorize
但忘了格林威治燃油丢弃计划那部分
but she left out the word eferring to the fuel duct in Greenwich.
你叫艾丽丝
Your name is Iris.
你的生日是9月17号
You're birthday is September 17th.
将军私下动用了一些关系
The General probably pulled some strings stationed your only son in Australia
把你的独生子安排到了澳大利亚  以远离战争
as far from the war as possible.
你刚接到电话  将军的晚餐预约取消了
Tell the General his dinner's been canceled   the call came in just now.
晚餐预约取消了
Your dinner was canceled.
你忘了燃油部分
You forgot the fuel dump.
谢谢你  艾丽丝  出去吧
Thank you   Iris. That will be all.
- 凯奇  动手吧 - 瑞塔
- Cage   Let's go. - Rita.
- 我们应该
- Let me just  - What are you doing?
好了  别再向他开枪了
Please   don't shoot him yet.
好吗?我们应该
Okay? Just
将军
General.
这场对话我们不是第一次进行
Th  this isn't the first time we've had this conversation.
就因为你非常固执
Cause that's  because you're  you're stubborn.
你不相信我告诉你的  卡特博士是正确的
You won't believe me when I tell you that Dr. Carter was right
敌人可以随意控制时间
That the enemy can manipulate time.
我们注定失败
The invasion will fail
无论你让多少战士去送死
no matter how many bodies you throw at it.
赢得这场战争的唯一办法就是
And the only way to win this war
找到"拟态"的核心能量
is by finding this power source within the cord
消灭它
and killing it.
而找到这种能量的关键
And the only means of finding it
就在那个保险箱里
is in that safe right there.
无论这场谈话我们进行多少次
No matter how many times that we have this conversation
你都不相信  明天敌人就会攻陷伦敦
you refuse to accept that the enemy breaks through to London tomorrow
我们会失败
and we lose.
败的干净彻底
We lose everything.
就算真是这样
Let's say for one moment
又怎么合理地解释
that I can't rationally explain
你这金口玉牙的本事
your impressive parlor tricks.
卡特博士说过...
Dr. Carter told me
需要活着的"拟态"(Mimics)它才能起作用
this device requires a live Mimic to work.
你要它有什么用
What use is it to you?
- 这是我的问题 - 正好相反
- That's my concern. - On the contrary.
按你说的  这是关系到全世界
According to you   this concerns the whole world.
那你会怎么做  如果你相信我刚才说的话
Well what would you do if you believed everything I just told you?
我会找到那个...Ω
- I would locate this  - Omega.
把它炸得粉身碎骨
And bomb it out of existence.
用这种思维模式跟它斗
You're not mentally equipped to fight this thing
永远赢不了
and you never will be.
现在怎么办
What do we do now?
不知道  还没到过这一步
I don't know. We've never gotten this far.
挺容易的
That was easy.
站住
Stop! Stop right there!
不许动
Don't move!
都不许动
Nobody move!
扔掉武器
Drop it!
这东西怎么用
What am I supposed to do this?
插进你的大腿
Stick it in your leg!
快
Do it!
凯奇  感受到了什么
Cage   what happened?
告诉我
Talk to me!
我感觉到它了  我正在往那去
I feel it   it  it's taking me there.
你看见什么了
What do you see?
是罗浮宫
It's  it's the Louvre.
的哪?还有其他的吗
Where? Where else?
我在罗浮宫里  好多的水
I'm inside now. It's flooded.
在往下去有个车库  博物馆地下的车库
I'm going down a garage   a garage underneath the museum.
能看见Ω吗
The Omega   do you see it?
它在巴黎
It's in Paris!
瑞塔
Rita!
你在干什么
What have you done?
你没事的  只是需要输血
You'll be fine. You just needed blood.
你不知道你在干什么
You don't know what you've just done.
我不能跟你闲聊
I'm not allowed to talk to you.
跟我一起的
I was with someone.
瑞塔・弗拉塔斯基  还活着吗
Rita Vrataski. Is she alive?
瑞塔・弗拉塔斯基?
Rita Vrataski?
拜托
Please.
告诉我
Just tell me that.
拜托告诉我
Please tell me.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我解开这东西最多用不了三分钟  凯奇
I was out of those things in three minutes flat   Cage.
你怎么了
What's wrong with you?
我以为你死了
I thought you were dead.
还没
Not yet.
抱歉  凯奇
I'm sorry   Cage.
不  等等
No! Wait   wait   wait!
我完了  没能力了
I'm out! I'm out!
我被输了血
They gave me blood!
失去那能力了
I lost the power.
能感觉到
I feel it.
我无法再重置时间了
I can't reset the day anymore.
必须杀掉Ω
We have to kill the Omega
赶在开战之前
before the invasion starts.
剩下不到三小时了
That gives us less than three hours.
及时赶到巴黎需要一艘载运机
We need a drop ship to get to Paris in time.
还需要更多的士兵
We need more soldiers too.
谁会疯狂到跟我们去巴黎
No one's crazy enough to follow us to Paris.
凯奇
Cage!
大家
Guys!
我们都在到处找你
We've been looking everywhere for you!
听我说
Just listen
因为找不到你法雷尔都快把我们折磨死了
Farell almost strung us up by our bullocks for losing track of you!
听着
Just listen.
听我给你们讲个故事
But you're gonna want to hear this story.
一开始听着肯定会觉得很荒唐
Now it's gonna sound ridiculous at first   but the
但是往下听  就会越来越觉得合理
longer I talk the more rational it's going to appear.
是吗
Yeah?!
知道我学校的名字
He named the school I went to
还说出了我二年级老师的名字
and then he tells me my second grade teacher
叫钩子波莉老师
was called Miss Pollyhook.
她不让他去厕所  害得他尿了裤子
She wouldn't let him go to the bathroom   made him wet his pants.
你闭嘴
Shut up!
听着  我就是告诉你们  他什么事都知道
Look   I'm telling you   he knows everything
我们所有的事
about all of us.
放屁
Bullshit.
是吗
Yeah?
他还说  你的名字不是福特
He says your name ain't really Ford.
福特其实是你的朋友
He says Ford was your friend
在参战的第一天就阵亡了
died in combat on his first day.
你代替了他  还给他家里人寄钱
You took his place   send your checks to his family.
隐藏得可够深的
You slippery bitch.
凯奇说敌人知道我们的计划
Cage says the enemy knows us too.
正在海滩等我们
They're waiting for us on the beach
我们都会死
and we all die.
那根本就是一场屠杀
The whole invasion is a slaughter.
真是好极了
Well   this is great.
战前动员做的不错
Really good confidence booster for tomorrow.
谢谢  凯奇
Thanks   cage.
我们还有机会  对吗
But we can change it   right?
我们肯定能做点什么
I mean   there has to be somethin' that we can do.
总会有取胜的办法的
There has to be  a way that we can win.
是有个机会
There is a chance.
但很渺茫
It's a slim one.
需要你们跟我走  马上
But it means coming with me   right now.
大家听着
Listen   pal.
我不管你知道多少我们的私事
I don't really care what you think you know about us.
我们刚认识你
We just met you.
凭什么让我们跟着你去打仗
Come on   why would we follow him into combat?
没指望你们跟我走
I don't expect you to follow me.
你们可以跟她走
I expect you to follow her.
这不是钢筋铁骨娘吗...J小队
That's the full metal bi  J Squad.
她是瑞塔・弗拉塔斯基
This is Rita Vrataski.
大家都叫她...对
Otherwise known as  Yeah   yeah.
凡尔登的天使
The Angel of Verdun.
好吧
Okay.
新的一天
It's a new day   people!
命运在召唤
Destiny calls.
这世界只要我们做一件事
The world expects only one thing from us:
取得胜利
That we will win!
如果你们今天不全力拚搏
Rest assured they enemy will thank you
最高兴的肯定是敌人
for not giving a hundred percent today.
J小队
Squad!
J小队去哪了
Where's J Squad?
好了  听着
Right   okay.
这个Ω  能随意控制时间
So this Omega   it controls time?
把这帮新世代的混蛋炸回老家
Exploding it into pieces and sending its bullocks back to where it came from!
就都结束了
And then we go home!
对  但它还有α保护着
Right   it's guarded by an Alpha
连它一起杀  明白
Just kill it   okay?
不
No!
你们没听凯奇说吗
You heard what Cage said.
不能杀掉α
Do not kill an Alpha.
杀掉α  Ω会把一整天重置一遍
If we kill an Alpha   the Omega will reset this whole day.
我们都不会记得这次谈话
We'll never even remember we had this conversation.
它们却知道我们
They're gonna know we're coming.
如果遇到α要杀我  那我该怎么做
So what am I supposed to do if one of those Alpha's is about to kill me?
为全队牺牲自己
Take a hit for the team.
我们空降之后
When we're on the ground
它们很快就会知道我们到了  我们没多少时间
there's not gonna be a lot of time before they know we're there.
要设置一个观察哨
We're gonna need eyes up here.
我参加  凯奇
I'm going in   Cage.
还有三十秒到达
Thirty seconds   still contact.
基梅尔
Kimmel.
不
No!
福特  快走
Ford! Let's go!
凯奇
Cage!
我们该走了
We gotta go!
跳
Drop!
凯奇  它们知道我们要来
Cage   they know we're coming in!
跳
Drop!
得挂上  弹出去
You're not hooked in!
你怎么那么慢
What took you so long?
还有活着的吗
Where are the others?
我们快没弹药了  我还有双刃砍刀
We're low on ammo   I've got one claymine.
福特  你没弹药了
Ford   you're out.
格瑞夫的弹药库只剩一半子弹了  而他也动弹不了
Griff has only got half a magazine left and he can hardly move.
你不是能看到未来吗
I thought you could see the future?
我刚来到今天
I haven't lived this day.
不知道会发生什么
I don't know what's gonna happen.
别纠结了
It doesn't matter.
想想怎么干掉它们
What matters is we finish this.
怎么干
With what?
格瑞夫不能动了  我们死了三个人
I mean   Griff can't even walk. We're three men down.
算了吧
Come on!
听着  别浪费时间了  集中弹药
Look   we're running out of time. Collect your ammo.
我们和金字塔之间有上千个"拟态"(Mimics)
There must be a thousand Mimics between us and that pyramid.
你说怎么做  难道直接走正门吗
So what are we gonna do? Just walk up to the front door   is that it?
不能待在这儿等死
If we stay here   we die.
是吗
Yeah?
肯定过不去
We'll never get through.
能过去的
We could.
用那个
In that.
那东西飞不起来
That ship will never fly.
不用飞起来
It doesn't need to fly.
只要能带着我们快速地
It just needs to get us across there
穿过那里就够了
with speed.
如果引擎还能启动 用动力杆操控就行
If the engines are still running   we could steer with the power levers.
斯金纳
Skinner.
清出一条路
Clear a path.
- 现在再试一次 - 不  还没反应
- Try it again now. - No   it's not reading.
状态控制杆拉低
Condition lever low.
主电源打开
Electrical power on.
格瑞夫
Griff!
我们要走了  快点
We gotta go! Come on!
我帮不上什么忙了
I'm not gonna be any good in there   mate.
让我给你们争取点时间吧
Let me buy you some time.
电源启动了
The power's on.
会成功的
This is gonna work.
喂
Hey!
快点!我们要走了
Hey   come on   man! We gotta go!
别等我们了
Don't wait for us!
斯金纳、格瑞夫  快点
Skinner   Griff   come on!
- 可以出发了  他们呢? - 斯金纳和格瑞夫呢
- We're good to go   where are they? - Where's Skinner and Griff?
他们不来了
They're not coming!
走吧  必须离开了
Go   brother. You gotta go   man.
我们下辈子再见吧
I'll see you in the next life.
见鬼!
Bullocks!
快闪开
Move over! Move over!
我们得走了
We gotta go!
我们必须离开了  快
No   we gotta go now!
他们来了  凯奇
They're coming   Cage.
死吧!你们这些混蛋
Die you bastards!
死吧!
Die!
重新装弹
Reload.
他们过来了
We've got incoming!
快点
Come on!
凯奇
Cage!
你来驾驶
You have to take over!
瑞塔
Rita!
加速
Push it! Push it!
这不是最惨的
We've been through worse.
好了
Okay.
它在那儿
It's there.
在水里  那儿
In the water   there.
是个α
That's an Alpha.
一会儿我负责把它引开
I'm gonna draw that thing away.
你负责杀掉Ω
You kill the Omega.
不
No.
你挪不了几步就会被它杀掉  凯奇
You won't make it ten feet before that thing kills you   Cage.
我能做到
I can do it.
拿着手榴弹
Take the grenades.
我能做到
I can do it.
听我说
Listen to me.
这次我们俩谁都逃不了
Neither one of us is getting out of here.
谢谢你
Thank you.
带我能到现在
For getting me this far.
你是个好男人  凯奇
You're a good man   Cage.
但愿能有机会好好了解你
I wish I had the chance to know you better.
欢迎来到伦敦  少校
Welcome to London   Major.
我是蒙哥马利下士
I'm Corporal Montgomery
布里格姆将军新闻办公室的联络官
the liaison to General Brigham's press office.
很高兴你能来
Very good to have you.
你看新闻了吗?
Have you heard the news?
就在今天黎明之前
Just before sunrise this morning
巴黎探测到一股强大的能量波
a large surge of energy was detected in Paris.
我们虽然还没有查明原因到底是什么
We do not know exactly what this signifies
但是结果却表明我们的敌人
but the result appears to be a total collapse of
已经完全丧失了战斗能力
the enemy's capacity to fight.
俄国和中国的军队正在横扫欧洲
Russian and Chinese troops are now moving across Europe.
一路所向披靡
Without resistance.
明天  我们将挺进西部前线
Tomorrow we advance on the Western front.
相信我们一定取得胜利  为我们自己
We believe we are marching to claim a victory for ourselves
为我们所爱的人
for our loved ones
为我们的同胞
for our countrymen
也为了整个人类
for the entire human race.
你们干什么的
What are you?
我们是战士
I'm a warrior!
战士该干什么
What do warriors do?
杀戮
Kill!
你们将该干什么
What are you gonna do?
杀戮
Kill!
你不可能参加过20场战斗
You haven't been in twenty battles   Ford.
当然有
I have too!
明天一到海滩  你肯定会吓傻的
You're gonna dump your load the second we hit the beach tomorrow   Ford.
拜托  你们俩能不能把臭嘴闭上
How about you two get yourselves a nice hot cup of shut the hell up?
小妹你真幽默
You funny   girl.
但我打赌  明天我会破纪录的
But I bet you I set some kind of record tomorrow.
是逃跑最快记录吧
Fastest time moving backwards for
别踩到自己拉的屎
slipping in your own shit!
你们是干什么的
Who are you standing for??
我们是战士
A warrior!
战士该干什么
What do warriors do?
杀戮
Kill!
立正
Attention!
怎么了
Yes?
有什么事
What do you want?
《明日边缘》片尾曲
约翰・纽曼  再爱我一次
我只想明白 明白
? I need to know now   know now ?
你能再爱我一次吗
? can you love me again ?
我只想明白 明白
? I need to know now   know now ?
你能再爱我一次吗
? can you love me again? ?
我只想明白 明白
? I need to know now   know now ?
你能再爱我一次吗
? can you love me again? ?
我只想明白 明白
? I need to know now   know now ?
你能再爱我一次吗
? can you love me again? ?
能再给我一次机会吗
我的行为无可原谅
? it's unforgivable ?
让你的身心深受打击
? I stole and burnt your soul?
这种行为和魔鬼无异吧
? is that what demons do? ?
我的心智被魔鬼所占据
? they rule the worst of me ?
让一切化为乌有
? destroy everything ?
让天使如你也受尽磨难
? they bring down angels like you ?
我鼓起勇气勇敢站起
? now I'm rising from the ground ?
向你发出疾呼
? rising up to you ?
血脉中鼓起了全部勇气
? Filled with all the strength I've found ?
如今的我无可阻挡
? there's nothing i can't do ?
好吧
? all right ?
我只想明白 明白
? I need to know now   know now ?
你能再爱我一次吗
? can you love me again? ?
我只想明白 明白
? I need to know now   know now ?
能再给我一次机会吗
? can you love me again? ?
好吧
? all right ?
哦  再来一次
? oh   come on ?
好吧
? all right ?
你能再爱我一次吗
? can you love me again? ?
明白 明白 明白 明白
? know   know   know   know ?
好吧
? all right ?
是啊
? yeah ?
哦
? oh ?
让这份爱继续 这份情延续 求你了
? i told you once I can't do this again ?
这份情延续 我求求你了
?do this again   oh   no ?